ZACHARY BRADLEY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Zzachbradleydev@gmail.com **3** zach-bradley.github.io/ **7** Hazleton, PA **in** zachary-bradley-2295646a/ **7** zach-bradley

Experienced full stack developer building applications with technologies and languages like JavaScript, Python, React, and various other major libraries. Experience working with and building API's for internal application use.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES: JavaScript, Python, TypeScript

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING: React, Node, MySQL, Redux, Firebase, NoSQL, RESTful APIs, Data Structures, Algorithms

PROJECTS

Recipe Macro Visualizer June 2020 - July 2020

- -Tools used: Python, Flask, SQLAlchemy, PostgreSQL, and an outside RESTful API.
- -Displays recipe breakdown are analyzed and displayed using the D3 library and allows the ability to save recipes for future use.
- -Capitalized on knowledge of SQL to develop custom tables and models.

Bar Finder with Google Maps Integration

Nov. 2020 - Dec. 2020

- -Tools used: JavaScript, React, Firebase, Google Maps API.
- -Integrated the Google Maps API to draw place data and display the map itself.
- -Makes use of Google's Firebase Firestore to store user data.
- -Built custom components from the ground up.

EMPLOYMENT

American Eagle Outfitters, Group Lead

Feb. 2020 - Current

Provide support to the distribution center Supervisors and coordinate and lead my team to better the workflow in my area.

Springboard, Software Engineering Fellow, Remote

Jan. 2020 - Jan. 2021

700- hour course that covers key aspects of front and back-end web development, databases, and data structures and algorithms.

American Eagle Outfitters, Operation Clerk

June 2019 - Feb. 2020

Work with products and databases to make sure the product is correct while solving any problems other associates have.

EDUCATION

Springboard [an. 2020 - Jan. 2021

Software Engineering Certificate

Luzerne County Community College

Associate's Degree Business Administration and Management

2016 - 2019

CERTIFICATES

Modern JavaScript Bootcamp, https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-HNDFA1ZC/

52 hour intensive course on modern JavaScript.

Web Developer Bootcamp Certificate, https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-6B7DHVA4/

46 hour course developing full stack applications

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Certificate,

https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-98266945-d769-4144-96de-df6821ff0617/

22 Hour Course on Data Structures and Algorithms